and she said, okay, what you need to
do is you need to tell a story.
Tell me a story. And I thought this
was a really interesting
way of explaining it, rather than kind
of fretting about language selection
and
all this kind of stuff.
Tell me a story. Because what I
realized is we can all
tell stories. So we tell stories to
our mates down the pub.
We tell like our partners, stories
about what happened at work.
When we were teenagers, we told our
parents stories, like when we got into
trouble.
Kind of like if the police find a body
under our patio, we have to tell some
kind of story, right?
So there's lots and lots of stories
and we know how to tell
those stories. We know how to kind of
pick that language.
And so what I sort of realized about,
even if it's non -fiction, it's the
same,
is you have to come up with a way of
telling the story about whatever it is
that
you're writing.